http://www.crimemagazine.com/privacy-notice

PRIVACY NOTICE Crime Magazine
Skip to main content
Sign In | Sign Up
AboutAdvertiseBlogsEponymous Rox's blogMichael Thomas Barry's blogBooks of NoteContactLinksStoreSubscribeWriters' Corner
MurderAssassinationsJFK AssassinationMLK AssassinationRFK AssassinationCold CasesMass MurderersSerial KillersWar CrimesCelebritiesForensicsHeistsJustice IssuesCapital PunishmentCorruptionRichard Nixon's CrimesHate CrimesInnocence CasesPrisonsOrganized CrimeBooks/FilmsSexMore...Crime StudiesForeign CrimesHistorical CrimesInvestigative ReportingKidnappingTrialsWild West
PRIVACY NOTICE
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for Crime Magazine.  This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site.  It will notify you of the following:
1.       What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
2.    What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
3.   The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
4.    How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you.  We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us.  We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship and process an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy. Please subscribe to our newsletter for news and promotional offers.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time.  You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
-          See what data we have about you, if any.
-          Change/correct any data we have about you.
-          Have us delete any data we have about you.
-          Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information.  When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way.  You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page. We currently use Pay Pal to process credit cards.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information.  The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 1-360-464-1909 or via email.
Total views: 26823
Justice on Fire
On the night of November 29, 1988, near the impoverished Marlborough neighborhood in south Kansas City, an explosion at a construction site killed six of the city’s firefighters. It was a clear case of arson, and five people from Marlborough were duly convicted of the crime. But for veteran crime writer and crusading editor J. Patrick O’Connor, the facts—or a lack of them—didn’t add up. Justice on Fire is OConnor’s detailed account of the terrible explosion that led to the firefighters’ deaths and the terrible injustice that followed. Also available from Amazon
On This Date in Crime History
John Wayne Gacy Confessed to Killing Dozens (December 22, 1978)
Tweets by @CrimeMagazine
Video
AuthorsJ. J. Maloney
Lisa Agnew
H. P. Albarelli Jr.
Jane Alexander
Betty Alt
Scott Thomas Anderson
Diane Anderson-Minshall
Mel Ayton
Joan Bannan
Michael Thomas Barry
Scott Bartz
John F. Kelly
David Kirschner, PhD.
Barbara Kussow
Marie Kusters-McCarthy
Doris Lane
Jason Lapeyre
Ronald J. Lawrence
David Lohr
Lora Lusher
Douglas MacGowan
Denise Noe
Lt. John Nores Jr.
J. Patrick O'Connor
John O'Dowd
Robert Phillips
Liz Porter
Kelly Pucci
Mark Pulham
Joe Purshouse
Patrick Quinn
James Rada Jr.
Randy Radic
Mirah Riben
Michael Richardson
David Robb
Ryan Ross
Eponymous Rox
Anneli Rufus
Laura Schultz, MFT
Cathy Scott
Fred Shrum, III
Ronnie Smith
Francesca Spina
Lynne Stewart
James A. Swan, Ph.D.
Benjamin Welton
Claudette Walker
Daniel B. Young
Evan Whitton
John Tait
Kim Walker
Marilyn Z. Tomlins
Michael Volpe
Conditions
AboutWith the purpose of writing about true crime in an authoritative, fact-based manner, veteran journalists J. J. Maloney and J. Patrick O’Connor launched Crime Magazine in November of 1998. Their goal was to cover all aspects of true crime: Read More
Contents Copyright © 1998-2020 by Crime Magazine | J. Patrick O'Connor Editor | E-mail CrimeMagazine.com
Designed by Orman. Drupal theme by ThemeSnap.com
